00-0000 All Occupations
11-0000 Management Occupations
11-1000 Top Executives
11-1010 Chief Executives
11-1011 Chief Executives
11-1020 General and Operations Managers
11-1021 General and Operations Managers
11-2000 Advertising, Marketing, Promotions, Public Relations, and Sales Managers
11-2020 Marketing and Sales Managers
11-2021 Marketing Managers
11-2022 Sales Managers
11-2030 Public Relations and Fundraising Managers
11-2032 Public Relations Managers
11-3000 Operations Specialties Managers
11-3010 Administrative Services and Facilities Managers
11-3012 Administrative Services Managers
11-3013 Facilities Managers
11-3020 Computer and Information Systems Managers
11-3021 Computer and Information Systems Managers
11-3030 Financial Managers
11-3031 Financial Managers
11-3050 Industrial Production Managers
11-3051 Industrial Production Managers
11-3060 Purchasing Managers
11-3061 Purchasing Managers
11-3070 Transportation, Storage, and Distribution Managers
11-3071 Transportation, Storage, and Distribution Managers
11-3120 Human Resources Managers
11-3121 Human Resources Managers
11-3130 Training and Development Managers
11-3131 Training and Development Managers
11-9000 Other Management Occupations
11-9020 Construction Managers
11-9021 Construction Managers
11-9040 Architectural and Engineering Managers
11-9041 Architectural and Engineering Managers
11-9120 Natural Sciences Managers
11-9121 Natural Sciences Managers
11-9160 Emergency Management Directors
11-9161 Emergency Management Directors
11-9190 Miscellaneous Managers
11-9199 Managers, All Other
13-0000 Business and Financial Operations Occupations
13-1000 Business Operations Specialists
13-1020 Buyers and Purchasing Agents
13-1020 Buyers and Purchasing Agents
13-1040 Compliance Officers
13-1041 Compliance Officers
13-1050 Cost Estimators
13-1051 Cost Estimators
13-1070 Human Resources Workers
13-1071 Human Resources Specialists
13-1080 Logisticians and Project Management Specialists
13-1081 Logisticians
13-1082 Project Management Specialists
13-1110 Management Analysts
13-1111 Management Analysts
13-1140 Compensation, Benefits, and Job Analysis Specialists
13-1141 Compensation, Benefits, and Job Analysis Specialists
13-1150 Training and Development Specialists
13-1151 Training and Development Specialists
13-1160 Market Research Analysts and Marketing Specialists
13-1161 Market Research Analysts and Marketing Specialists
13-1190 Miscellaneous Business Operations Specialists
13-1199 Business Operations Specialists, All Other
13-2000 Financial Specialists
13-2010 Accountants and Auditors
13-2011 Accountants and Auditors
13-2050 Financial Analysts and Advisors
13-2051 Financial and Investment Analysts
13-2090 Miscellaneous Financial Specialists
13-2099 Financial Specialists, All Other
15-0000 Computer and Mathematical Occupations
15-1200 Computer Occupations
15-1210 Computer and Information Analysts
15-1211 Computer Systems Analysts
15-1212 Information Security Analysts
15-1230 Computer Support Specialists
15-1231 Computer Network Support Specialists
15-1232 Computer User Support Specialists
15-1240 Database and Network Administrators and Architects
15-1241 Computer Network Architects
15-1244 Network and Computer Systems Administrators
15-1250 Software and Web Developers, Programmers, and Testers
15-1252 Software Developers
15-1290 Miscellaneous Computer Occupations
15-1299 Computer Occupations, All Other
15-2000 Mathematical Science Occupations
15-2030 Operations Research Analysts
15-2031 Operations Research Analysts
15-2050 Data Scientists
15-2051 Data Scientists
17-0000 Architecture and Engineering Occupations
17-2000 Engineers
17-2040 Chemical Engineers
17-2041 Chemical Engineers
17-2050 Civil Engineers
17-2051 Civil Engineers
17-2070 Electrical and Electronics Engineers
17-2071 Electrical Engineers
17-2072 Electronics Engineers, Except Computer
17-2080 Environmental Engineers
17-2081 Environmental Engineers
17-2110 Industrial Engineers, Including Health and Safety
17-2111 Health and Safety Engineers, Except Mining Safety Engineers and Inspectors
17-2112 Industrial Engineers
17-2130 Materials Engineers
17-2131 Materials Engineers
17-2140 Mechanical Engineers
17-2141 Mechanical Engineers
17-2170 Petroleum Engineers
17-2171 Petroleum Engineers
17-2190 Miscellaneous Engineers
17-2199 Engineers, All Other
17-3000 Drafters, Engineering Technicians, and Mapping Technicians
17-3010 Drafters
17-3019 Drafters, All Other
17-3020 Engineering Technologists and Technicians, Except Drafters
17-3023 Electrical and Electronic Engineering Technologists and Technicians
17-3024 Electro-Mechanical and Mechatronics Technologists and Technicians
17-3025 Environmental Engineering Technologists and Technicians
17-3026 Industrial Engineering Technologists and Technicians
17-3027 Mechanical Engineering Technologists and Technicians
17-3028 Calibration Technologists and Technicians
17-3029 Engineering Technologists and Technicians, Except Drafters, All Other
19-0000 Life, Physical, and Social Science Occupations
19-2000 Physical Scientists
19-2030 Chemists and Materials Scientists
19-2031 Chemists
19-2040 Environmental Scientists and Geoscientists
19-2041 Environmental Scientists and Specialists, Including Health
19-3000 Social Scientists and Related Workers
19-3010 Economists
19-3011 Economists
19-4000 Life, Physical, and Social Science Technicians
19-4030 Chemical Technicians
19-4031 Chemical Technicians
19-4040 Environmental Science and Geoscience Technicians
19-4042 Environmental Science and Protection Technicians, Including Health
19-4043 Geological Technicians, Except Hydrologic Technicians
19-4090 Miscellaneous Life, Physical, and Social Science Technicians
19-4099 Life, Physical, and Social Science Technicians, All Other
19-5000 Occupational Health and Safety Specialists and Technicians
19-5010 Occupational Health and Safety Specialists and Technicians
19-5011 Occupational Health and Safety Specialists
19-5012 Occupational Health and Safety Technicians
23-0000 Legal Occupations
23-1000 Lawyers, Judges, and Related Workers
23-1010 Lawyers and Judicial Law Clerks
23-1011 Lawyers
27-0000 Arts, Design, Entertainment, Sports, and Media Occupations
27-1000 Art and Design Workers
27-1020 Designers
27-1024 Graphic Designers
27-3000 Media and Communication Workers
27-3030 Public Relations Specialists
27-3031 Public Relations Specialists
29-0000 Healthcare Practitioners and Technical Occupations
29-1000 Healthcare Diagnosing or Treating Practitioners
29-1140 Registered Nurses
29-1141 Registered Nurses
33-0000 Protective Service Occupations
33-1000 Supervisors of Protective Service Workers
33-1020 First-Line Supervisors of Firefighting and Prevention Workers
33-1021 First-Line Supervisors of Firefighting and Prevention Workers
33-2000 Firefighting and Prevention Workers
33-2010 Firefighters
33-2011 Firefighters
33-9000 Other Protective Service Workers
33-9030 Security Guards and Gambling Surveillance Officers
33-9032 Security Guards
33-9090 Miscellaneous Protective Service Workers
33-9091 Crossing Guards and Flaggers
37-0000 Building and Grounds Cleaning and Maintenance Occupations
37-2000 Building Cleaning and Pest Control Workers
37-2010 Building Cleaning Workers
37-2011 Janitors and Cleaners, Except Maids and Housekeeping Cleaners
37-3000 Grounds Maintenance Workers
37-3010 Grounds Maintenance Workers
37-3011 Landscaping and Groundskeeping Workers
41-0000 Sales and Related Occupations
41-1000 Supervisors of Sales Workers
41-1010 First-Line Supervisors of Sales Workers
41-1012 First-Line Supervisors of Non-Retail Sales Workers
41-3000 Sales Representatives, Services
41-3090 Miscellaneous Sales Representatives, Services
41-3091 Sales Representatives of Services, Except Advertising, Insurance, Financial Services, and Travel
41-4000 Sales Representatives, Wholesale and Manufacturing
41-4010 Sales Representatives, Wholesale and Manufacturing
41-4011 Sales Representatives, Wholesale and Manufacturing, Technical and Scientific Products
41-4012 Sales Representatives, Wholesale and Manufacturing, Except Technical and Scientific Products
41-9000 Other Sales and Related Workers
41-9030 Sales Engineers
41-9031 Sales Engineers
41-9090 Miscellaneous Sales and Related Workers
41-9099 Sales and Related Workers, All Other
43-0000 Office and Administrative Support Occupations
43-1000 Supervisors of Office and Administrative Support Workers
43-1010 First-Line Supervisors of Office and Administrative Support Workers
43-1011 First-Line Supervisors of Office and Administrative Support Workers
43-3000 Financial Clerks
43-3020 Billing and Posting Clerks
43-3021 Billing and Posting Clerks
43-3030 Bookkeeping, Accounting, and Auditing Clerks
43-3031 Bookkeeping, Accounting, and Auditing Clerks
43-3050 Payroll and Timekeeping Clerks
43-3051 Payroll and Timekeeping Clerks
43-3060 Procurement Clerks
43-3061 Procurement Clerks
43-4000 Information and Record Clerks
43-4050 Customer Service Representatives
43-4051 Customer Service Representatives
43-4150 Order Clerks
43-4151 Order Clerks
43-4160 Human Resources Assistants, Except Payroll and Timekeeping
43-4161 Human Resources Assistants, Except Payroll and Timekeeping
43-4170 Receptionists and Information Clerks
43-4171 Receptionists and Information Clerks
43-5000 Material Recording, Scheduling, Dispatching, and Distributing Workers
43-5030 Dispatchers
43-5032 Dispatchers, Except Police, Fire, and Ambulance
43-5060 Production, Planning, and Expediting Clerks
43-5061 Production, Planning, and Expediting Clerks
43-5070 Shipping, Receiving, and Inventory Clerks
43-5071 Shipping, Receiving, and Inventory Clerks
43-5110 Weighers, Measurers, Checkers, and Samplers, Recordkeeping
43-5111 Weighers, Measurers, Checkers, and Samplers, Recordkeeping
43-6000 Secretaries and Administrative Assistants
43-6010 Secretaries and Administrative Assistants
43-6011 Executive Secretaries and Executive Administrative Assistants
43-6014 Secretaries and Administrative Assistants, Except Legal, Medical, and Executive
43-9000 Other Office and Administrative Support Workers
43-9060 Office Clerks, General
43-9061 Office Clerks, General
47-0000 Construction and Extraction Occupations
47-1000 Supervisors of Construction and Extraction Workers
47-1010 First-Line Supervisors of Construction Trades and Extraction Workers
47-1011 First-Line Supervisors of Construction Trades and Extraction Workers
47-2000 Construction Trades Workers
47-2010 Boilermakers
47-2011 Boilermakers
47-2050 Cement Masons, Concrete Finishers, and Terrazzo Workers
47-2051 Cement Masons and Concrete Finishers
47-2060 Construction Laborers
47-2061 Construction Laborers
47-2070 Construction Equipment Operators
47-2071 Paving, Surfacing, and Tamping Equipment Operators
47-2073 Operating Engineers and Other Construction Equipment Operators
47-2110 Electricians
47-2111 Electricians
47-2150 Pipelayers, Plumbers, Pipefitters, and Steamfitters
47-2152 Plumbers, Pipefitters, and Steamfitters
47-4000 Other Construction and Related Workers
47-4090 Miscellaneous Construction and Related Workers
47-4090 Miscellaneous Construction and Related Workers
47-5000 Extraction Workers
47-5010 Derrick, Rotary Drill, and Service Unit Operators, Oil and Gas
47-5020 Surface Mining Machine Operators and Earth Drillers
47-5022 Excavating and Loading Machine and Dragline Operators, Surface Mining
49-0000 Installation, Maintenance, and Repair Occupations
49-1000 Supervisors of Installation, Maintenance, and Repair Workers
49-1010 First-Line Supervisors of Mechanics, Installers, and Repairers
49-1011 First-Line Supervisors of Mechanics, Installers, and Repairers
49-2000 Electrical and Electronic Equipment Mechanics, Installers, and Repairers
49-2090 Miscellaneous Electrical and Electronic Equipment Mechanics, Installers, and Repairers
49-2094 Electrical and Electronics Repairers, Commercial and Industrial Equipment
49-3000 Vehicle and Mobile Equipment Mechanics, Installers, and Repairers
49-3030 Bus and Truck Mechanics and Diesel Engine Specialists
49-3031 Bus and Truck Mechanics and Diesel Engine Specialists
49-3040 Heavy Vehicle and Mobile Equipment Service Technicians and Mechanics
49-3042 Mobile Heavy Equipment Mechanics, Except Engines
49-9000 Other Installation, Maintenance, and Repair Occupations
49-9010 Control and Valve Installers and Repairers
49-9012 Control and Valve Installers and Repairers, Except Mechanical Door
49-9040 Industrial Machinery Installation, Repair, and Maintenance Workers
49-9041 Industrial Machinery Mechanics
49-9043 Maintenance Workers, Machinery
49-9044 Millwrights
49-9060 Precision Instrument and Equipment Repairers
49-9069 Precision Instrument and Equipment Repairers, All Other
49-9070 Maintenance and Repair Workers, General
49-9071 Maintenance and Repair Workers, General
49-9090 Miscellaneous Installation, Maintenance, and Repair Workers
49-9096 Riggers
49-9099 Installation, Maintenance, and Repair Workers, All Other
51-0000 Production Occupations
51-1000 Supervisors of Production Workers
51-1010 First-Line Supervisors of Production and Operating Workers
51-1011 First-Line Supervisors of Production and Operating Workers
51-2000 Assemblers and Fabricators
51-2090 Miscellaneous Assemblers and Fabricators
51-2090 Miscellaneous Assemblers and Fabricators
51-4000 Metal Workers and Plastic Workers
51-4040 Machinists
51-4041 Machinists
51-4080 Multiple Machine Tool Setters, Operators, and Tenders, Metal and Plastic
51-4081 Multiple Machine Tool Setters, Operators, and Tenders, Metal and Plastic
51-4120 Welding, Soldering, and Brazing Workers
51-4121 Welders, Cutters, Solderers, and Brazers
51-8000 Plant and System Operators
51-8020 Stationary Engineers and Boiler Operators
51-8021 Stationary Engineers and Boiler Operators
51-8090 Miscellaneous Plant and System Operators
51-8091 Chemical Plant and System Operators
51-8093 Petroleum Pump System Operators, Refinery Operators, and Gaugers
51-8099 Plant and System Operators, All Other
51-9000 Other Production Occupations
51-9010 Chemical Processing Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9011 Chemical Equipment Operators and Tenders
51-9012 Separating, Filtering, Clarifying, Precipitating, and Still Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9020 Crushing, Grinding, Polishing, Mixing, and Blending Workers
51-9021 Crushing, Grinding, and Polishing Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9023 Mixing and Blending Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9040 Extruding, Forming, Pressing, and Compacting Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9041 Extruding, Forming, Pressing, and Compacting Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9050 Furnace, Kiln, Oven, Drier, and Kettle Operators and Tenders
51-9051 Furnace, Kiln, Oven, Drier, and Kettle Operators and Tenders
51-9060 Inspectors, Testers, Sorters, Samplers, and Weighers
51-9061 Inspectors, Testers, Sorters, Samplers, and Weighers
51-9110 Packaging and Filling Machine Operators and Tenders
51-9111 Packaging and Filling Machine Operators and Tenders
51-9120 Painting Workers
51-9124 Coating, Painting, and Spraying Machine Setters, Operators, and Tenders
51-9190 Miscellaneous Production Workers
51-9198 Helpers--Production Workers
51-9199 Production Workers, All Other
53-0000 Transportation and Material Moving Occupations
53-1000 Supervisors of Transportation and Material Moving Workers
53-1040 First-Line Supervisors of Transportation and Material Moving Workers
53-1047 First-Line Supervisors of Transportation and Material Moving Workers, Except Aircraft Cargo Handling Supervisors
53-3000 Motor Vehicle Operators
53-3030 Driver/Sales Workers and Truck Drivers
53-3032 Heavy and Tractor-Trailer Truck Drivers
53-3033 Light Truck Drivers
53-7000 Material Moving Workers
53-7010 Conveyor Operators and Tenders
53-7011 Conveyor Operators and Tenders
53-7050 Industrial Truck and Tractor Operators
53-7051 Industrial Truck and Tractor Operators
53-7060 Laborers and Material Movers
53-7062 Laborers and Freight, Stock, and Material Movers, Hand
53-7065 Stockers and Order Fillers
53-7070 Pumping Station Operators
53-7072 Pump Operators, Except Wellhead Pumpers
53-7120 Tank Car, Truck, and Ship Loaders
53-7121 Tank Car, Truck, and Ship Loaders
