Loading EIA Refinery Capacity Report...
Calculated NCI for 126 refineries from EIA data.
Loading facilities.json...
No NCI match found for: Paulsboro Refining Co LLC - Paulsboro
No NCI match found for: Enterprise Prod Texas Operating LLC - Mont Belvieu
No NCI match found for: Hartree Refining LLC - Channelview
No NCI match found for: Pasadena Refining Systems Inc - Pasadena
No NCI match found for: Targa Downstream LLC - Mont Belvieu
No NCI match found for: Trecora Hydrocarbons LLC - Silsbee
No NCI match found for: Tesoro Refining & Marketing Co - Anacortes
DEBUG Sinclair Wyoming: {
  stateMatches: [
    'HF SINCLAIR CASPER REFINING COMPANY - EVANSVILLE (Wyoming)',
    'WYOMING REFINING CO - NEWCASTLE (Wyoming)',
    'SILVER EAGLE REFINING - EVANSTON (Wyoming)'
  ],
  bestMatch: 'HF SINCLAIR CASPER REFINING COMPANY - EVANSVILLE (Wyoming)',
  bestScore: 32,
  foundExact: false
}
No NCI match found for: HF Sinclair Wyoming Refining Co - Sinclair
Successfully matched NCI for 123 out of 158 facilities.
Updated facilities.json with NCI data.
